There's a book that I read on my
travels, have been reading. I've read it
at least 10 times, Awareness by Anthony
de Mello.
>> I love that book. Fantastic book.
>> It's such a good book and different
things hit you at different times. He
was a Jesuit priest, also a
psychotherapist. The density, I would
say, of insights per page on this is
just incredible. It's very easy to read,
it's very funny, it's very short. It's
only about 170 pages. Once again, I'm
reading it and different things are
popping out at different points in life
and I actually have multiple hard copies
that I've highlighted at different
points and the highlights are different
things. The passages that resonated at
different points in time. If you suffer
from anxiety or depression or if you
just feel like you have a little too
much edge, you're running a little fast,
you feel a little overcommitted,
clogged, stuck at points, whatever it
might be, this book is fast-acting
medicine and it's not a panacea, but
it's really complimentary for almost
anything else that you would do
to help with the types of symptoms that
I just described, which are really
symptoms of modern living.